Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Unidentified man (Box 4, Folder VPC.00789)
  Description: Unidentified man possibly giving a talk. Facing let, with left arm bent into a right angle
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00790)
  Description: Unidentified man collecting a fecal sample from a goat? He is smiling and wearing a plaid shirt.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- 2 Unidentified men, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00791)
  Description: 2 unidentified men facing each other in front of a car. The man on the left is reaching into his breast pocket and holding a folder. The man on the right is crossing his hands in front of him. See also VPC.00464
- Wedding couples, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00792)
  Description: Unidentified couples dancing at a wedding
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, n.d. (Box 4, Folder VPC.00793)
  Description: Close up of an unidentified man. He has a small mustache, crooked teeth (only a few are seen) and a receding hairline. The stain on the photograph is in his right ear
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 10.5", 1 print on cardboard
- 2 Unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00794)
  Description: 2 unidentified men holding horns from an animal hanging on a wall. One of the men is also pictured in VPC.00779.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5 " x 5.5", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified couple, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00795)
  Description: Unidentified couple. He is holding a pair of glasses. She is holding a purse and glasses.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8", 5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Two unidentified men at the beach, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00796)
  Description: Candid of two unidentified men at the beach. One may be Myron Fincher
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 8", 2 prints on cardboard
- Unidentified man about to shake hands, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00797)
  Description: Unidentified man facing right about to shake hands with an unpictured man.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 2 prints on paper"
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00798)
  Description: Unidentified man looking almost straight at photographer. He is squinting and has a small mustache. He is wearing a suit and tie.
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00799)
  Description: 2 unidentified men in a living room, possibly in a fraternity house. One is seated and the other is standing in front of a fireplace under a portrait
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00800)
  Description: Unidentified man standing in front of a white wall. He is crossing his arms and smiling.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 6", 1 print on cardboard
- 2 unidentified men speaking at the Hotel Hamilton, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00801)
  Description: Two unidentified men at a podium at the Hotel Hamilton. Notation on original envelope says "printed 12/3/62" See also VPC.00293 and VPC.00298.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00802)
  Description: Unidentified older man in a barn with cows. He is holding a suspended G.E. electrical device.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00803)
  Description: An unidentified man seated in a chair drinking from a tea/coffee cup with his left hand on his leg
- Unidentified Man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00804)
  Description: Unidentified man speaking at a conference with NEW YORK written behind him.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00805)
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00806)
  Description: 2 unidentified men outside a telephone booth
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7", 5.5" x 8.5" (cropped), 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00807)
  Description: Unidentified man standing behind desk flipping through papers with a desk light above them
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 6", 10" x 10", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00808)
  Description: Unidentified man standing in front of white wall and wood. His head is slightly turned right and he is looking at the camera
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 8.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- 3 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00809)
  Description: 3 unidentified men at a conference table in a library.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 10", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00810)
  Description: Unidentified man in a lab coat using a blender in the lab.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 9.5", 10" x 10", "1print on paper 1 print on cardboard
- 2 unidentified men at a softball game, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00811)
  Description: 2 unidentified men at a picnic. One is ready to run, the other is standing with his hands on his hips. Looks like a softball game.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 8.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00812)
  Description: Unidentified man facing right and no glasses. There are chairs in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7"x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00813)
  Description: Unidentified man with glasses looking at the camera, seated with one hand in his pocket, the other on his leg. There's a piano behind him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00814)
  Description: 2 unidentified men standing in front of a truck
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00815)
  Description: 2 unidentified men standing in front of the Moore Laboratory
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 12", 8.5" x 12", 1 print on paper, 1 print on particle board"
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00816)
  Description: Unidentified man wearing glasses and a hat. He has a pen and a piece of paper in his pocket. Fincher?
- 3 unidentified people in a buffet line, 1964 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00817)
  Description: 3 unidentified people ( 2 women and 1 man) in a buffet line.
- Buffet, 1964 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00818)
  Description: 2 unidentified men and women getting food from a buffet.
- Unidentified couple at a buffet, 1964 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00819)
  Description: Unidentified man and women getting food from a buffet.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00820)
  Description: An unidentified man facing left, wearing a light suit and glasses. He is touching his fingers slightly together. Another man is on the left, but is cut off
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9.5", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man and dog, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00821)
  Description: Unidentified man in a sweater holding out a dog's leg (boxer?)
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5", 3 prints on cardboard
- 2 Unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00822)
  Description: 2 unidentified men at a sitting at a table, with papers and a book in front of them.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9"x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Students in a lab, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00823)
  Description: Unidentified student filling up a tube with water in a lab
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8"x 10", 1 print on paper
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00824)
  Description: 2 unidentified men looking down and right. They are both wearing glasses, suits and ties. There's a fire hose behind them.
- Two unidentified men, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00825)
  Description: 2 unidentified men exchanging a piece of paper in front of a car. One is wearing a plaid shirt, the other a hat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: Size. 9.5" x 9.5", 7.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- 2 unidentified women and a man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00826)
  Description: 2 unidentified women and a man at a dinner table. One woman is touching the man's head and holding a napkin.
- Students dissecting, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00827)
  Description: 3 unidentified students dissecting animals in the lab. One, on the far right, is a woman.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 6.5", 5" x 7", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Joe Kane, ca. 1950s (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00828)
  Description: Joe Kane with a dog on a sidewalk
- Colonel William Jennings, ca. 1960s (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00829)
  Description: Col. William Jennings with a ribbon on his jacket holding a paper
- Harold Nadler (and I. W. Swall?) (Box 4, Folder VPC.00830)
  Description: Candid of Harold Nadler and two unidentified men. Is one I. W. Swall?
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 13", 6" x 9.5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- W.A. Hagan and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00831)
  Description: W.A. Hagan and unidentified man
- John Bentinck-Smith, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00832)
  Description: John Bentinck-Smith bending over a table
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 transparency"
- Unidentified building, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00833)
  Description: Unidentified building
- Moore Lab from the rear in winter, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00834)
  Description: Moore Lab from the rear in winter
- Unidentified building in winter, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00835)
  Description: Unidentified building in winter
- Moore Lab from the front in winter, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00836)
  Description: Moore Lab from the front in winter
- Garage in winter, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00837)
  Description: Garage in winter
- Peter Kennedy, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00838)
  Description: Peter Kennedy outside James Law Hall in winter. Photo used in college pictured in VPC.00716.
- Dr Crawford and wife, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00839)
  Description: Dr Crawford and wife
- Maurice M. Jastremski, 1962 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00840)
  Description: Maurice M. Jastremski sitting in from of a New York State Veterinary Medical Society sign.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5", 4" x 6", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Marion Newson, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00841)
  Description: Marion Newson, staff artist
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7", 6" x 6", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Student Group, 1937 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00842)
  Description: Pictured, left to right: Dorney, Zeissig, Hagan, unidentified man, Marie Koenig, unidentified, Ethel Eaton, Wilson Bell, Leonard Goss, unidentified, P.P. Levine, Cordy, W.S.Stone, William Monlux, unidentified, Olafson, Lynn Potter, Ba
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 15", 7" x 13", 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard, 2 transparencies
- Unidentified - In the Field (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Unidentified - Two People (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Unidentified - Dogs, Cats, Racoons, Horses (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Unidentified - Cows and Sheep (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Unidentified - Children (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Unidentified - Dining (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Unidentified - Dancing (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Unidentified - Large and Formal Groups (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Unidentified - Women (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Unidentified - Misc. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Ellis Leonard, Class of 1934 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Donald W. Baker with Students (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Dr. Delahauty with Students (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Dedication of Dr. Denny H. Udall Oil Painting, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 14)
- William Hagan (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
- Alums: Harold Cooper, Class of 1938 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Alums: Roger Batchelder, Class of 1946 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Alums: George McConnel and Dr. Matthias Kemen (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Alums: Dr. Stephen Roberts, Class of 1938 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Al Raney, Class of 1932 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Walt Matusajak, Class of 1940 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Dr. Bruce Widger, Class of 1951, and Mrs. Mary Widger (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Unidentified Misc. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Unidentified Misc. (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Unidentified Misc. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- Unidentified - Iman (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Misc. Small Photos (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Negatives (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Unidentified - Picnic (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Fred Kilborne, Class of 1885 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- John Louis Halloran, Class of 1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- James Law (Box 5, Folder 8)
- W.A. Hagan, E.W. Tucker, Cassius Way (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Unidentified - Iman (Box 5, Folder 9)